Kettle and Idol
What do you mean by video editing?
Well, I opened a personal TikTok account last year.
I opened a TikTok account,
And the reason why I decided to open a TikTok account,
Recently, some of our members have been using Twitter and TikTok, and some of them have been using other means of communication,
I was still working on Instagram, or distributing my own content, or doing other things,
I was still only doing Instagram and streaming,
I had only Instagram, distribution, and so on,
I wanted to start TikTok,
I decided to start TikTok,
I thought I would like to start TikTok, but the main thing about TikTok is that you dance to music on a screen close to the screen,
I thought I might not be able to do that,
But when I thought that I might not be able to do that, I decided to make a vlog.
I wanted to make a vlog of the routines of my live performances,
I took pictures of the scenery and other things when I went on an expedition,
I thought it would be a good idea to edit them into a video and post it,
That's when I started editing videos,
I started editing videos and sometimes edited the group's videos as well,
From there, it was amazing.
When I'm at home or on vacation, I've been doing a lot of video editing.
I mainly edit videos at home when I'm not working.
That's great!
So you do all your video editing and filming
You do it all on your smartphone?
Yes, I do.
I use my smartphone.
I have a video editing app.
I connect to it and play music,
I also add some sound effects here and there,
I've recently learned how to do that,
I've been editing my videos as a way to practice,
I used TikTok when I was on an expedition to Okinawa,
I made a vlog called "Okinawa Expedition Vlog",
I had to calculate or think about how to make the video change to the song,
fans told me that I was getting better at editing the video,
I was very happy that they understood my work.
Are there any editing techniques that you would like to try in the future, or that you think would be fun to try or that you would like to imitate from watching others?
For example, before, I used to erase all the talking of the members and only put in the music,
But recently I've been thinking that it would be better to include the sounds of the members' daily life and their conversations,
For example, the size and color of the letters may change depending on the tension of the conversation.
When you watch TV or YouTube videos, for example.
I thought it would be fun to do something like that for the viewers,
I'm learning a little bit about it.
I see, you are getting more and more out of sync.
I'm not quite there yet.
But I'm having a lot of fun with it, and I'm doing it as a hobby, but I read in a horoscope book this year that it would be good to do some video editing.
How can I get you to do that? My horoscope book says I should do video editing, and my horoscope book says it's a good idea.
I saw that you should expand your hobbies.
I thought it was video editing.
I kind of forgot about that.
So, I started.
Then I thought it was in a book on divination.
I killed two birds with one stone.
It was written in a book of horoscopes.
Yu Yu Yu Yu
oil oil oil oil oil
Yu-Yu-Yu
This program is
Mr. Sasaki
Mr. Daidaippanpan
Mr. Ebi no Fuji
Meow-chan
Thank you to Fuuji-san for providing this program!
Thank you very much for your contribution today!
thank you!